Ujiran Michinoku no Starlust, I'm Inoue and Aku's Yasumori-waka!
And I'm Pototakara or Male Actor, the eternal 30 year old active idol, Shinya Aiwa!
Please.
Nice to meet you. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I've already been to a few rehearsals.
But I didn't know what to call you yet.
I've been standing on the wall with you for a long time, haven't I?
But you really have a great aura.
No one is that mature.
I don't know what to say about you guys.
I'm always called "Komprehend.
If you could just call me "Kikkun.
I'll call you "Komprehend.
You can call me Chami, which is my nickname.
Cute, Chami.
You can call me anything.
You can also call me by my name.
Then, let's call me Mr. Chami.
Because it feels distant.
Please let it be at least Mr. Chami.
Please let me call you Chami-sama.
Thank you very much.
This is Mr. Chami.
We will be performing at Tokyo Night Land Vol. 3 on September 6
We will be performing at Uguishi Sasa ni Bara.
And what a surprise, this time we have a former member of the Takarazuka Revue
Ms. Aya Hane, who is still active on the stage
I would like to learn makeup from Chami-sama.
Yay.
I've been training with the idols for a long time.
I thought that Takarazuka makeup would definitely suit them.
They all have such beautiful and wonderful faces.
I was really looking forward to it.
Of course, I had never done anything like that in my life, soOf course, I've never done anything like that in my life.
I'm a little nervous.
I look forward to working with you today.
This time, I would like to show you a little bit of Waka Rin's face that you have never seen before.
I'd like to show you a little bit of Waka Rin's face that you have never seen before.
I'd like to start with the makeup, but I'd like to have the makeup artist do it under the guidance of Ms. Ainu Hane.
I'm very excited to see what you have to offer.
I'm very excited and I'm looking forward to seeing you.
I've never heard of it, but I've never heard of it. I've never heard of it.
Yes, I've never heard of it before.
Where do you apply the stage makeup?
This is used as a foundation, and the brown color is often used as a nose ring, like the coloring used in Takarazuka's makeup, and this is used as a blush.
And blush is applied to the forehead and forehead, and blush is put inside.
Wow!
On stage, especially at Takarazuka, the spotlights can make your face fly off if you use light makeup.
To prevent that, I'll wear heavy makeup.
It's been too long since I've shown my face without makeup.
It's been too long since I've shown you all my face without makeup.
I'm usually a gal.
Oh, that's right, you wear a lot of makeup.
I've been trying not to show too much, but this time I really want to show you guys this makeup.
I'm glad, but when it's done, it's going to be darker than a gal's.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so happy!
Then, I'm going to use about 5 times as much foundation as I normally use.
Five times?
5 times?
Apply it as if you were covering the entire face with 1mm of foundation.
Please.
Good boy, good boy, good boy.
Like a pat, pat, pat, pat.
Like you're going to tap it on.
That's good.
This is the color for male actors, number 9.
For example, the makeup for a female actor like Oskar would be a bit whiter.For example, the makeup of a daughter actor or Oskar, for example, is a little bit whiter.
Oh, so there is a difference in color?
Yes, the color is changed depending on the role.
Paint so much that you lose the original face.
That's scary.
It's like a face painting.
I call it "war".
There's a revolution going on.
Like the French Revolution.
Skin like the French Revolution
Yuko Kainin
Revolution.
A revolution is happening.
Revolution is happening.
Did I apply it at all?
It's perfect.
There's not a millimeter of the original skin left.
You can't even make a pretty face now.
I'm scared.
Now we're going to do the nose job.
This color is 2C.
Brown.
You can use your ring, middle or index finger.
Take a little bit on your belly, and with two fingers, do this.
Wow, wow, wow.
Apply it like this.
It's hard to do, so you can do it one at a time.
I want to have a taller nose.
I asked for it.
My nose will never be taller.
At the base of the eyebrows.
Start here, where it dips.
From there.
Straight from there.
Straight down, not outward.
Straight down to the bottom.Straight down to the bottom.
It's a little bit on the inside.
It was inside.
You're laughing.
Funny remote control, isn't it?
That's funny.
Straight up, straight up.
And then it's a straight line all the way in.
That's it.
I'm getting better.
That's good.
Now, from here, don't go inwards. Blur it outwards.
Blur it gently with your fingers.
Do you Takarazuka performers do your own makeup?
Yes, they do.
With a makeup artist?
No.
We have to do about 80 people at once for a performance.
If I had a makeup artist, I wouldn't be able to do it.
So I have to do it by myself.
When I was in music school, I learned how to do it once.
And you learned makeup at that time, too.
Once they teach you how to do it...
After that, we'll do it ourselves at our own school.
It's not like there's a makeup class or anything.
There's one time when the older students come to the school and teach us.
Heh...
I see.
How's your nose?
My nose is so shiny.
It's probably the biggest swoosh of my life.
Well, I guess I'll just go with it from now on.
Laughs.
I'm going to keep it like this from now on, just to make it look shinier.
I'm definitely going to do this from now on.Now then, you should definitely go.
LOL.
I will live in Kamahana.
Yay!
It's perfect.
Yes, it's OK.
Oh, cool.
Yeah, it is.
It looks good.
You're starting to look good in that pose.
All right. - All right.
Okay, okay.
Next, this red number 4C...
In Takarazuka, if you don't wear makeup well...
The lighting can really make your face pop.
If you just put a little blush powder on top...
If you just put a little powder on top, it'll all fly off and you'll end up looking completely white.
That's why we put blush inside.
It's like the color comes from the inside.
First, take the same amount of blush as the nose.
Start from the high part of the cheek here.
Up to here on the forehead.
Up to the forehead.
All the way up to the forehead.
I'm so nervous.
Up to the forehead, please.
Oh, I see.
It can be darker.
I'm afraid it'll look like a flag.
Flag? What country?
Flag?
It's gonna look like a flag.
What country's flag?
I didn't know there was a country called "Flag".
There's so many flags floating around.What a lot of buoyancy!
Nice sensibility
Fun
It's fun
I love it.
And this sponge is fine as it is.
please blur it out!
The face is so clear at this point.
It's starting to look a little like Takarazuka, isn't it?
It already looks like Takarazuka.
It's beautiful.
She's smiling a lot.
After all this time...
I'll dust a little more.
A little bit more.
Usually, you only need a little bit of powder.
It's so white, it's like tempura.
Tempura.
I'm getting to the point where I think of it as tempura.
Please apply as much as you want.
I wonder if I'm going to be given a raise.
Until it's super matte.
I'll hold them back.
Let's do it now.
Here we go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Yes, yes, it's good.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's just right.
And then we'll make sure that this fits all the way in.
Okay.
Tap it in.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Perfect.Perfect.
It's matte, it's amazing, it's tempura, it was tempura, it's amazing, it's tempura, it feels like tempura, right?
Oh, it's not sticky. It's not sticky anymore.
It's a little bit fixed, isn't it? It's fixed. It's fixed.
It's fixed, it's fixed, it's fixed.
This is not enough. We're going to paint the heart from here.
Next is this. This is called a face cake. Cake? Yes, it turns your face into a cake.
It's like a normal foundation, but we'll put some water on it and pretend it never happened.
Pretend it never happened?
I've painted it black and red, but it'll probably look like it never happened.
Is that okay? You're going to do that? Yes, but it will look great in the light and in the end.
You use purified water, dissolve it in a sponge, rub it off, rub it off, rub it off, rub it all over.
Okay. Oh, that's the center.
And then, actually, I apply it to the neck and ears as well.
Ears?
I see.
I see, the color is different, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, it looks good. You've painted it!
I think this is the face you don't want to be seen in this state.
What should I do?
Shall I put a mosaic?
It's the smoothest face.
It's true that everything up to this point looks like it was done just now.
Yes, it's going to get more and more gorgeous from here.
The base is done here.
Here is the base.
Yes, the base!
Yay!
Let's start with the eyebrows.
Let's start from the top.
We'll use four eyebrows for the gradient.
Oh, wow!
There's this, uh, color called ABC, black ABC.
This is the gradation.
The lightest color, C, is thicker first.The lightest color, C, is first made thicker.
Bold, clear, and cool.
You can bend your eyebrows more and more.
Oh, yes, let's go there.
You can draw them 1.5 times as thick as the final thickness.
1.5 times?
Yeah.
It'll be like this.
That's because the original is quite thick.
If it becomes like this...
It'll be like this.
It's cool.
You drew it to a great extent.
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't worry, you can go ahead and draw all the way out.
I do a lot of my own makeup.
Eyebrows are the key to gal makeup.
In my case, I use thin, parallel eyebrows.
Thin parallel eyebrows
I don't make them that long.
They're definitely short.
I don't have long eyebrows.
I have quite a few female fans of my eyebrows.
They ask me a lot of questions.
I want to have baby eyebrows.
How do you draw them? I get a lot of questions like, "How do you draw your eyebrows?
It's a totally different eyebrows.
I'm so sorry to all the eyebrow fans.
My eyebrows are totally different.
I want to discover new eyebrows!
What am I going to do today, when I get these eyebrows next time?
I've been a fan of eyebrows for a long time.
That's good.
Then next time, I'll use color B.
One size smaller.
A millimeter smaller.Smaller, about 1 mm each.
Draw it again.
Inward
Like a gradient inward.
How long have you been a gal?
When I realized...
I wasn't aware of it at first.
So Tohoku-san has always been a group that doesn't wear makeup?
Without makeup?
Yes, we sang and danced with no makeup on.
When did everyone start... when was that?
When they were all in high school?
They were all rebellious.
The rebellion!
Shut up!
Yes, they wanted to grow up.
You want to wear makeup.
It's a girl's prerogative, isn't it?
I wanted to wear a strong woman's makeup.
I wanted to wear the makeup of a strong woman.
So I started wearing that makeup.
I got a reaction from clients and people who had never seen me before that there was a gal in the show.
I thought I was a gal.
I thought I was a gal, and that's when I became a gal.
You really didn't know you were a gal?
You were a gal when you found out?
Yes, I did.
My mindset is gal, too.
So I really started out as a gal by the way I looked.
Perfect!
Next, let's do this A.
One more inside.
Like a yellow pencil.
I'm going to write here.
If I had started with natural makeup
I might not be a gal now.I might not have been a gal now.
I might have a different personality.
I might have been a girl.
I might have been
I might have had a different personality.
Now that I'm in Takarazuka makeup.
I might start talking like a male actor
I might start talking like a male actor.
If you're the type to start with looks...
That's true.
I'm the type that tends to dye easily.
Do you think you'll be okay? For the past fans...
You're in the middle of your rehearsal period, right?
There's an event in Tohoku, too.
I'm a little conscious of it.
I'm usually hunched over.
I've been warned about it.
I've been thinking that I need to fix it myself.
But during rehearsals, everyone has a really nice back.
When I think I have to be conscious of it
I think I should be conscious of it.
Maybe I should practice all the time.
Maybe you're right.
This is a great start.
I hope it does.
One more thing.
It's all black now.
I'm going to make it thicker in the middle.
You're so particular about your eyebrows alone, aren't you?
Yes, it's like a painting, right in the middle.
Now let's move on to the eye makeup.
This is where it changes the most.
The biggest change is right here.
First, put white all over the eye holes.
The inner part of the eyes and the tear ducts.Inside and at the tear ducts.
Paint all the way down to the whites of your eyes.
It's more like an eyeshadow or a paint palette.
So many colors.
Green, green, green, green.
Everyone's free to choose their own eyeshadow.
That's right.
Any color you like.
Some use Shu Uemura.
Paint it on really thick.
My face has a deep moat.
It's already a little bit done.
I'm so happy.
I've been watching a lot of Takarazuka videos during this period.
The male actors are really cool.
I'm glad I'm getting used to it.
I'm already used to it.
They're all doing a great job.
Do you have a point, or a key to playing Andre?
Exaggerate.
Oh, my God.
I didn't say anything.
Oh, great.
Oh, misery.
Unhappy.
Oh, my God.
A lot of the male roles are over the top.
I think they can all do great natural acting.
But they're male roles, and they're different genders.
And their age is probably different from their real age.
And they're from different countries and different nationalities.
I'm trying to be something completely different.
And I want to be as good as Takarazuka, where you're bathed in spotlights and wear glamorous costumes, and I want to be as good as Takarazuka.
I want to be as good as Takarazuka with the spotlight and the glittering costumes.It's as good as a place called
star with dignity.
Try it.
I love you.
I love you
Make it bigger than that.
That's good.
I love you.
That's great.
Is this really free to watch, so far?
Okay, repeat what you said.
You want a thousand vows?
You want 10,000 oaths.
10,000 vows will get you 10,000 vows will get you 10,000 vows will get you 10,000 vows
I have only one word for you
I love you.
What is this?
I wanted to do it.
I wanted to.
Thank you.
It's got the right direction.
It's going to get better.
You've got a lot of pressure on your words.
Yes, I wish you would have said that.
I was hoping you'd say that. Next is a double line.
Four dabs of pink.
A little thicker, a little thinner.
It'll be fine right here.
The border.
White and skin tone.
And on top of that.
A little thicker.A little thicker.
I think there is a strong image that eyeshadow is very blue.
If a Caucasian's eyes are blue, he wears blue eyeshadow.
I see.
The color inside the eyes can be changed.
Nowadays, there are contact lenses and so on.
But you don't change the color of the inside of the eyes, but express it with eye shadow.
That's amazing.
Yes, that's good.
Okay, now put it on the inside.
A little bit of water and a thin line of blue.
Oh! Here we go.
It's like you're going inside the pink.
I like it.
It's going to look like Takarazuka all at once with this line.
Everyone's makeup is a little different, depending on what they want to look like, so I'm not sure if my makeup is right for everyone.
So I don't think I'm doing everything right.
There are many more ways to do it.
I put pink at the corner of my eyes, and then I put a little bit of pink on the outer corner of my eyes.
I draw the highline a little bit too far from my eyes.
That's as far as your eyes go.
I'm going to go to a ridiculous amount of places.
The part I just painted on the big swamp is also about a waste villa.
Like a white stain line.
Yes, that's right.
It's nice.
Yes, it is.
Then, the blue would be about the same size as the current one in the middle of the river.
Yes.
You're playing a male role, aren't you?
Like Patarillo?
Let's see..,
Patarillo.
You don't know Patarillo?
I don't know.I don't know.
I'm of the generation that doesn't know Patarillo.
Patarillo.
Do you know Patarillo?
I don't know.
I don't know what is Patarillo.
Do you know Patarillo?
Yes, I do.
Oh, thank goodness.
I'm from a generation that doesn't know about Patarillo.
Let's see, there's "Haikarasan Dori" and so on.
Oh, Haikara-san comes through.
That's good, that's good.
It's the same generation.
I was watching Yuzukarei's movie.
Yes, yes.
Haikara-san coming through.
You know, a lot of the guys in those beautiful shoujo manga are pretty straight-eyed.
Heh.
There are beautiful men, but I want them to be beautiful but in a "tale-me" kind of way.
I see.
Yes, that's the image I had in mind.
Then, a little lower.
Yes, at the corners of the eyes.
Yes, yes, even down to the bottom.
So that's what you're going to do.
Don't you remember your regular makeup? Like this?
Oh, on the contrary, I haven't learned my usual makeup from anyone,
I want to learn.
I see.
Next time, I'll do gal makeup. Gal Corser. I've never done galcoser.
Gal Corser is a must. Please do. Next time. Yay! I'm glad.
It looks good. Very nice. Now let's go to the eyeliner.
I think I'll start with the light blue. The reason why I'm applying the light blue first is because the light blue color comes out more beautifully if I apply the white color first. I see.I think I'll start with the light blue. The reason why I am painting the light blue first is because the light blue color comes out more beautifully if I paint the white color first. Oh, I see.
That's the only reason, so you don't even need the white. Please change all the white to light blue.
Shocking, isn't it? It's amazing that you did this by yourself. I'm really surprised. It's probably the biggest surprise of all. Surprise, right?
Surprise.
Next, eyeliner!
I have a double folded eyelid, so I use a lot of eye tape to make a double folded eyelid.
I have a very beautiful parallel double fold, so I'm going to keep it as it is.
This is a special kind of eyeliner called "Lubotin Line" which is very thick.
It's like Menu Pure.
It's really thick.
I don't know why it's so much darker than the normal black eyeliner
I don't know why it's so different
I don't know why, but when I use Lubotin, it looks more like Takarazuka.
It's a mysterious eyeliner.
It's so thick!
A little bit...
First of all, don't open your eyes until it dries.
Yes! Scary!
You'll get it on the color.
Close your eyes once.
Apply it to the inside of your current double width.
Once you've done that, apply the same width to the inner and outer corner of your eye.
From the inner corner of the eye
It's cold.
It's a liquid, so it's very thick.
This is...
Treasure Jane's. Even after all these years, I still can't breathe.
I'm so focused.
Oh, my God.
I do it myself.
When I'm already talking to the juniors, too.
Even if they have something to do with the seniors.
I'm in Lubotin.
I can't call out to them anymore because they're like, "Oh, I'm in Lubotin right now.
And the person who is doing it is so concentrated that he can't hear anything.
I hold my breath and write.I hold my breath and write.
It's like don't talk to me.
It's like you're really in the middle of a button.
I don't push my whole body.
It's powerful.
I can use it in my daily life.
Wait a minute.
I'm on the button, so shut up.
It's so good!
Strong words.
And I'm gonna dry this off.
You know...
Some people use a hair dryer to dry their hair.
I dry it by hand.
I dry it with my hands.
Ah! Nice sound!
I found something good!
What is this?
This is official Uguisudani no Bara merchandise!
What? You suddenly want to introduce goods here?
All of the members of the cast have one of these.
Oh, I want to see it!
The back is decorated with roses, just like the ones in Takarazuka.
The back is decorated with roses!
Why are you using this one now?
How much is this?
1,000 yen!
This one will be sold for 1,000 yen.
There will be a very exciting scene if everyone buys one.
Please buy it!
Now, let's dry it off!
Oh, wow! Great air volume!
It's so big!
It's cool, folks!
It's still going to work!It looks like it will still work!
This is nice!
Not visible, but totally!
Are we done?
Yes, did you open it?
Okay, open the first one!
Open it!
Ready!
Ta-da!
Oh! Yes!
Oh! Cute!
Cute!
Come here!
Cute! Awesome!
Amazing!
Such a big inner ring!
Wow! This is how they were dried!
That's nice!
And now, an extension of the open eye
This inner extension, in the shape of a "ku".
My eyes aren't too far apart to begin with.
I'm fine with the super inner side.
It's so sharp!
You have the image!
It's amazing!
The "U" shape.
First of all, you just put this here.
Heh!
And here...
like this.
And here
Yes!
All the way to the outside.
You don't need to put so much inside.
I think it's an okay refill.I think it's an okay refill, so
I'm just a little concerned about this place.
What do you call it?
It's like an A on the corner.
Yes!
Yes! Yum!
Yum!
That's good!
It's good.
Oh!
That's great!
Then I'll draw the bottom line.
The bottom line should be in robin brown.
And then we'll do the bottom line in brown.
From the apex of this arch
From the apex
Like this.
That's right.
And then draw it like this.
And then I want to draw the lower lashes.
You want to draw it?
Yes, draw them.
You're going to fill in here?
Fill it in. It's fine.
So you want to make the eyes bigger?
I'm going to make them really big.
Enormous!
I took a purikura once with Takarazuka makeup on.
It was amazing.
How big were they?
Go outside.
It's okay to go outside.
Don't go down there.
That's good.That's good.
Maybe I can get one before this.
That's good.
That's great.
And then I'll put mascara on and then I'll put the lashes on.
Yes, sir.
On the day of... yeah.
It looks good.
And then I'm going to ask you to close your eyes for the lashes.
I'd like to apply the lashes as if the outermost part of this eyeliner is the edge of the eye.
Like putting it on the outermost edge of this eyeliner.
I don't want to put it on the lashes, but I want to put it on the eyeliner.
Think of the eyeliner as your eyes.
This is the first time in my life that I've worn false eyelashes!
My debut as a fake eyelash stylist!
I'll start here.
Okay.
Good luck.
Today...
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's in the wrong place on the lash line.
I know.
I'm gonna open your eyes one more time.
It's good.
I like it.
It looks great.
You look great.
It doesn't look that different.
It's the same.
It's just the way I am.
It's because I'm deeply chiseled.
It won't change that much.
Then I'll put on a little blush.
A little lipstick, and you're done.
Just blush.Blush only
Shading.
This bone line.
I want to put it right here.
Right here.
That's good.
Now, let's put on the lipstick.
You make lipstick?
Yes, I do.
I have some that I've already made.
I want it to be this color.
I see.
I guess it depends on the role and the costume.
Depending on the role and the costume.
I see.
I want to change the color to match the role.
What color would suit you?
Beige with a hint of blush.
Oh!
Thank you.
Oh, wow.
Oh, that's great paint!
Paint.
Wow.
Oh, but there was a little more. Sorry.
I have to make an outline.
Huh?
That's good.
Okay, here's the real last one.
The last one is the one I just used for the eyebrows.
Thank you.
First, I'll draw the fujibitai.
Fuji?
What did you say?
Fujivitae.
Fujivitai?Fujibitai?
Fujibitai?
Fujibitai means "forehead of a horse mackerel".
Wow, that's the first I've heard of it.
I've never heard it before.
When you wear a wig, like Maiko-san, you get this pictogram.
Oh, yes, yes, yes...
Here in the middle is "fujibitai".
Hee...
It looks cooler with this part.
I see.
So, the way to draw it is, you start with the right side.
And then, a little bit on the left side.
This is the first time I've done this.
Next, contouring is really important for a manly face.
Men's foreheads are not round but square.
So we're going to put a horizontal line here.
Straight across.
No diagonals.
Right angle.
That's right!
Split up and keep it that way.
Keep it at that length.
Higher up.
All the way up.
I can't get in!
Oh, my God!
Straight up.
It doesn't matter if you make it round.
I'd be a girl.
That's good!
Yes! Yes!
That's great!
Yes!Good!
Souvenirs inside.
Keep this shape.
It's like stretching it this far.
That's good!
That tickles!
Good!
It's like a connection... from the inside.
Perfect! That's great!
Now the Takarazuka make-up is complete!
Thank you!
Yay!
It looks great on me!
I'm so excited!
It's perfect!
I haven't seen it yet.
Let's see it when I get my hair done, shall we?
Now let's see the makeup for Hanashi Waka's Takarazuka!
Please!
Here we go!
The three of us will go!
And now, let's see the male actress, Hanashi Wakarashi!
Three, two, one.
Go ahead!
Wow! So cool!
Oh, it's so cool!
It's so cool!
I haven't seen it myself yet.
I'm not sure how it's going to turn out, guys.
I think it's really cool!
I'll mix the windows.
Wow!
Well, let's have a look, shall we?
May I? Thank you very much.
Here we go! Ready!Here we go! Ready!
Eeeee!
Wow!
What do you think?
What a surprise!
It looks great on you.
What? I can't believe your skin tone.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, of course.
Wow, that's amazing!
I've never seen myself like this before.
Oh, my gosh!
The bridge of my nose is really
It's so much higher now!
Wow!
My eyes have doubled in size!
The rise is amazing!
Her hair style is amazing!
I know, this makeup looked great on me.
But the moment she did her hair
All the people around me were going, "Wow!
Wow, he's so cool!
Amazing! Amazing!
It looks great on you, doesn't it?
It looks great on you.
Amazing!
You really look like you belong in Takarazuka!
I'm so happy!
I think the point is to make the bridge of the nose
The point is to make the bridge of the nose higher
And the outline of the face to make it look more masculine.
And the eye makeup.
The eye makeup should be thick and strong.
Make it big and crisp
To make it stand out.
Even with eyelashes like this.Even if you do your eyelashes like this
To make you look like a man
To make him look like a man.
And lastly, I'm going to do this hair.
to make it stand up properly.
to make him look cool.
Like a guy in a shoujo manga
Like a guy in a girl's manga.
I want to draw a picture on his face.
like a painting on a canvas.
Wow, that's great.
That's great.
I did the traditional Takarazuka nose-jointed pose
I've been trying to do a traditional Takarazuka nose-jointed pose.
I'd love your guidance.
Then I'll spread my legs.
Yes, sir.
And twist a little bit.
Twist.
Pelvic twist, body forward.
Forward?
Pelvis stays this way, upper body a little forward.
Yes, that's good.
And now your left hand.
To the right.
Oh, great, great, great, great.
And right hand to the lower back.
Oh, great, great, great.
And then the left
It's kind of like a JoJo stand.
It's also like a jojo stand
And the left leg is bent
That's good.
That's great.
I see.
This is the nose-jointed pose.This is the nose assembly pose
It's so good.
I'm not an idol.
LOL!
That's amazing.
You've become Mr. Music.
I'll incorporate it in Mr. Tohoku's music.
Great. Please do.
Where can we put it?
I have a song called "Tenkaichin
There is a song called
In the song
They do the Sendai pose.
Each of them
at the Momoshiki Utagassen
I'm so happy
At that time
Let's go, suddenly Tohoku-san!
We did it!
It's decided!
I'm so happy!
So, everyone, let's meet at Uguisunari no Rose for Nighttime Land Vol. 3
See you at Uguisunari no Rose!
10 points!
Yes, okay, thank you very much!
That was fun.
Great, 10 points, great!
That's a tough one.